https://www.ashtonslegal.co.uk/

Lending a helping hand...
when you need it most
We're with you...
Wills | Tax & Trusts | Property
*Merry Christmas & Happy New Year from Ashtons Legal! Our offices will be closed from 1pm on 24 December and will reopen at 8.30am on 4 January. There will be contingency plans in place if you need urgent legal help, so please call our usual switchboard numbers.*
Welcome to Ashtons Legal
Businesses only survive and thrive if they deliver what their clients and customers want. At Ashtons Legal, our aim is to be a firm you are proud to call ‘your solicitors’ and are happy to recommend to others. Whether you are a commercial client or an individual client, and whatever your legal needs, our focus is on always delivering first-class legal advice with exceptional service.
Close
How can we help you?
Please fill in the form and we’ll get back to you as soon as possible or to speak to one of our experts call
0330 404 0749
Your Name
Your Email
Telephone Number
Your Enquiry
How did you hear about us?
---Google SearchBing SearchGoogle AdvertLaw Society Website1 SchemePersonal/Friend RecommendationProfessional RecommendationSocial MediaThomson LocalYellow Pages/Yell.comOtherCan't Remember
Preferred Office
---Bury St EdmundsCambridgeIpswichLeeds (only French Legal offered here)Norwich
I accept that my data will be held for the purpose of my enquiry in accordance with Ashtons
Privacy Policy
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google
Privacy Policy
and
Terms of Service
apply.
‘Law Firm of the Year’ at national LawNet awards. Read more
Your Life
Your Life
Your Business
Your Business
Your Injury
Your Injury
A team to be proud of
Ashtons Legal ‘has the edge in client care’.
Legal 500
I have used many lawyers in my lifetime, for various things, but you and your team are one of the best that I have ever used! You were always professional and on the other end of the phone when I needed you (and I know that was quite a bit).
Ashtons Legal client
The ‘well-respected’ Ashtons Legal is ‘one of the leading firms’ in Suffolk and the Eastern counties.
Legal 500
They handle high-value work with the skill and dexterity of the main players in central London.
Chambers & Partners
I couldn't recommend these lawyers highly enough: they were integrity personified
Chambers & Partners
I cannot express how grateful I am – I’ve been so anxious and you have always given me advice support & kindness. You have earned my very sincere admiration. Thanks so much.
Ashtons Legal client
Your firm has been the simplest and easiest firm we've had the pleasure of dealing with.
Ashtons Legal client
Thank you for everything done both front and back of house, and trust me, I will recommend this brilliant company to anyone I know that needs your help
Ashtons Legal client
Thank you for all you efforts and guidance in relation to securing the purchase. The attention to detail, communication and overall professionalism was exceptional from you, your team and Ashtons Legal in general so thank you again!
Ashtons Legal client
Meet the team
Improving lives around us
You look to us for legal solutions which represent good value for money and are delivered in an effective and friendly way. We aim to go a step further and provide a consistently exceptional client experience to everyone who chooses to seek our advice.
Quality
Client Care
Respect
Communication
Employee Focus
Insights
Injury News
£50,000 compensation obtained for Norfolk lady injured by a horse
Read more
News for Individuals
Drivers’ hours law: some urgent relaxations to address supply chain issues
Read more
Injury News
£250,000 obtained for amputee
Read more
Business News
The UK’s new points-based immigration system – 7 things employers need to know…
Read more
Read More Insights
Twitter
Investors in People Gold
Lexcel
Legal 500 - Top Tier Firm
2018 LawNet Best BD/Marketing Winner
LawNet approved firm
Search site
How can we help you?
Search
Contact our office
Bury St Edmunds Offices
01284 762331
Cambridge Offices
01223 363111
Ipswich Offices
01473 232425
Leeds Offices
01133 931930
Norwich Offices
01603 703070
Make an enquiry
Please fill in the form and we’ll get back to you as soon as possible or to speak to one of our experts call
0330 404 0749
Your Name
Your Email
Telephone Number
Your Enquiry
Preferred Office
Bury St EdmundsCambridgeIpswichLeeds (only French Legal offered here)Norwich
How did you hear about us?
---Google SearchBing SearchGoogle AdvertLaw Society Website1 SchemePersonal/Friend RecommendationProfessional RecommendationSocial MediaThomson LocalYellow Pages/Yell.comOtherCan't Remember
I accept that my data will be held for the purpose of my enquiry in accordance with Ashtons Privacy Policy
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
Your choice regarding cookies on this site
We use cookies to optimise site functionality and give you the best possible experience. Clicking the Accept All button means you are accepting analytics and third-party cookies (check the full list). To control which cookies are set, click Settings.
Accept All
Settings
Our use of cookies.
You can learn more detailed information in our Privacy Policy
Some cookies are essential, whilst others help us improve your experience by providing insights into how the site is being used. The technology to maintain this privacy management relies on cookie identifiers. Removing or resetting your browser cookies will reset these preferences.
Essential Cookies
These cookies enable core website functionality, and can only be disabled by changing your browser preferences.
Google Analytics Cookies
Google Analytics cookies help us to understand your experience of the website and do not store any personal data. Click here for a full list of Google Analytics cookies used on this site.
Third-Party Cookies
Third-Party cookies are set by our partners and help us to improve your experience of the website. Click here for a full list of third-party plugins used on this site.
Accept All
Save & Close
